Your fan edits
have blown me away. I really cannot walk
5 ft without getting recognized.
All because someone on Tik Tok started
adding laser beams to my eyes and an
Alvin and the Chipmunks voice when I
talk. I have a personal policy that I
never ever ever say no to a selfie
request or an autograph or whatever.
Because when I say that that my success
is only because of you and people like
you, I mean it.
But anyway, I wanted to show you a
couple of the uh
of the fan edits that are out there that
we've had so much fun with.
Can we cut to some of those?
This is a tattoo.
A tattoo that Chris Riley got on his
leg.
I I didn't even know what to say.
I'm I'm humbled. I'm not sure that
you're going to want a tattoo of my
pouting face
20 years from now, but listen, I'm
humbled and flattered.
>> [laughter]
>> You can't force hummus up someone's
rectum, for example.
Right?
You can't
>> You know, they learned I was a beta had
an irrational fear of insects. And so,
they put him in a coffin.
>> And they dumped a box of cockroaches in
there with him.
And then closed the coffin. And they
left him in there for 10 days just with
a diaper.
>> You can't do that. Nobody told you you
had permission to do something like
that.
You know, and waterboarding was supposed
to be
the ultimate
technique.
But there were a couple that were
that were clearly worse than
waterboarding.
>> Uh sleep deprivation.
Right?
>> So
this was the first one that I received.
I I didn't even receive it. I just
randomly saw it on Instagram and
there are a lot of crazy talented people
out there. So I'm very very flattered,
but it's just nuts to me that
people are using their talents for silly
things like this. Thank you for that.
Oh my god. I have an assistant uh who
goes through my emails uh just because I
get hundreds and hundreds and hundreds
of emails every day. I I just can't get
through them.
And she told me the other day
"You know, you get you get nudes like
every single day." She said, "I just
delete delete delete."
And I said, "Yeah, safer that way." I
mean, I don't know if these people are
18 years old and even still I I don't
want their nudes.
And she said, "Oh, they're between like
and 70."
I was like, "Yeah, no."
There's even a a petition that somebody
started to put me on Dancing with the
Stars.
It's just so ridiculous.
I don't even know what to say.
I am
I am grateful though. I really am.
It's fun.
>> Of all these cameos,
what was the sweetest one?
>> Uh
I've gotten three. I've I've done about
1,950 cameos so far.
>> Okay.
>> I do 20 or 30 a day.
>> I've gotten three where Well, let me let
me back up. About 50% of them are
birthday wishes. You know, uh Jimbo's
birthday is next Tuesday. I say, "Hey,
happy birthday, Jimbo. John Kiriakou
here. Hope you had a great day, you
know, etc."
So, there's birthday, you know, Mother's
Day, Father's Day, whatever.
Advice.
Pep talk.
About 10% are pep talks. So, of the 10%
that have been pep talks,
three
have come back to say that I somehow
talked them out of committing suicide.
I'm not really sure how I did that.
But, you know, there are a lot of really
hurting people out there.
We get so wrapped up in our own lives,
in our own existences, we don't realize
how many other people are in pain.
There's one girl, she's just one out of
almost 2,000 Cameos that I've done.
One who sounded like she was in such
pain. I said, "Listen." In the Cameo, I
said,
"We're not supposed to do this, but
here's my phone number.
>> Wow.
>> Call me."
And she called me,
crying. She's 15.
She's bulimic.
Her parents don't understand her. She
was going to commit suicide.
And I talked her out of it.
And um she's called me twice since then.
Usually for less than a minute or two.
>> Very respectful.
>> Very, very respectful. And she said she
just she's having a down day and she
needs to hear a friendly voice.
And that's it.
Cameo has literally changed my life. Uh
Cameo is an app where, you know, D-list
celebrities,
people most Americans have never heard
of, like me, um
will give you birthday wishes, as I
said, or or a pep talk, or advice, or,
you know, happy Father's Day, or Merry
Christmas, or whatever.
But, every once in a while, you know,
people who are really in crisis reach
out because it's the only way they can
figure out how to get to you,
and then one thing leads to the other. I
I will add that during COVID, I had a
friend, a good friend, who took his own
life.
And I spoke to him the day before
he did that.
And
he sounded great. And I said to him,
"James, you sound great today." He was
He was depressed a lot.
And he said, "Yeah, I feel really good
today."
The next day his sister called me.
And um
and she said, "I wanted you to know that
James killed himself last night."
He um
he went for a walk in the neighborhood.
The neighbor had a big oak tree.
He strung up a noose, and he hung
himself from the neighbor's oak tree.
He left a note. He said he didn't want
to
get his mom's house dirty. But he said,
"Please call John and tell him I said I
was sorry."
I will never forgive myself
thinking that there was something I
could have done, something I could have
said to talk him out of it. Again, I had
talked him out of it, I don't know how
many times.
But
it made me realize how many people
are out there who are genuinely hurting.
And if they need a friendly voice,
and I happen to be that friendly voice,
I'm happy to do it.
We've got to rely on each other. I think
COVID really
really showed that to all of us, that we
have to help each other and stick
together to get through these tough
times. We can't just be focused on our
own lives and stuck in our own zone when
there are other people out there who
really need help.
And so I I was glad
that I could help somebody.
I am addicted [music] to Angry Birds.
>> My ex-wife once told me that one of the
reasons why she wanted a divorce was
because as soon as my alarm goes off in
the morning, I roll over, put on my
glasses, pick up my phone, and I start
playing Angry Birds. And she would lose
her mind on me. What are you doing? Are
you playing Angry Birds again? Is that
all you do is play Angry Birds? In my
defense, I actually get up an hour
early. Nobody's missing out on anything.
I'd rather have Angry Birds than have
you. I'm globally ranked on Angry
[music] Birds.
>> I have played 2,887
consecutive [music] days.
>> A guy said to me the other day, "Hey, I
made level 36 in Angry Birds. What level
are you?" I said, "1,708."
Angry Birds [music]
is very important to me.
>> [laughter]
>> The more
podcasts I'm on, the more people ask me
about my personal life. And one of the
things that I love, love, love, it's
really my only vice, besides buying art,
um is playing Angry Birds. Angry Birds
2.
I have not missed a single day in nine
consecutive years. I love Angry Birds.
It's the first thing I do when I wake up
in the morning. I roll over, I put on my
glasses, I get my phone, I go to Angry
Birds, and I start killing those pigs
that are eating my birds' eggs.
And of course, I use
the black pearls that I accumulate to
buy hats for my birds, and I increase
the number of feathers so their flock
strength is more, and you have to you
have to know Angry Birds to really
understand. But man, there is nothing
that I love more than Angry Birds. You
got to love Angry Birds. It's For For a
while, it was like the only joy I had in
life.
And sure enough,
the first thing I did this morning was
play Angry Birds. I will add that my
doctor, last time I went in for a
physical, my doctor said, "You know,
you're 61, you're almost 62. You need to
start thinking about keeping your brain
fresh. And I said, "Okay, what do you
mean by that?" And he said, "I want you
to do the New York Times crossword
puzzle every day." I said, "Every day,
including Saturday? Cuz that's like an
impossible puzzle."
He said, "Yeah, do it every day."
I've become obsessed with crossword
puzzles. I do the Washington Post, which
is really the LA Times. I do the New
York Times. I do the USA Today every
single day, 7 days a week. So, now I
have to actually get up even earlier
because I do the I do the crossword
puzzles first, and then I do Angry
Birds. Because Angry Birds, you know, I
can take breaks and, you know, whatever.
Check out Angry Birds.